A Deliciously Fun Holiday Movie Adventure!
The Yummy Gummy Search for Santa is a animation
film directed by Jurgen Korduletsch.
The internet’s favorite musical candy bear brings his sense of fun
and creativity to an exciting search for Santa.
Will he find him in time?
Gummibär (voice), played by Sonja Ball.
Vam Piro (voice), played by Rick Jones.
Harry (voice), played by Bruce Dinsmore.
Allen (voice), played by Mike Paterson.
Kala (voice), played by Holly Gauthier-Frankel.
Narrator/Rudy (voice), played by Terrence Scammell.
Gummibär (pronounced [ˈɡʊmibɛːɐ̯] ; German for "gummy bear") or Gummy Bear is a German Eurodance multilingual character and virtual musician
that performs gummy bear-related songs on various albums, including I Am Your Gummy Bear (2007) and La La Love to Dance (2010).
The video for the song "I'm a Gummy Bear" and its Spanish version has 3.7
billion and 1.3 billion views on YouTube respectively.
The film explores themes of santa claus, alien,
cartoon bear, christmas, holiday special.
The tone is lighthearted.